[Music]
Road accidents are daily problems for
cities causing disruption delays and
congestion but how exactly does this
occur Road speed and traffic flow data
derived from Singapore's land transport
Authority were combined with information
about the location and timing of traffic
accidents here we are able to explore
the Dynamics of this disruptive behavior
pink circles identify accidents blue
heavy traffic and orange
vehicle breakdowns this data can be fed
into simulation models that allow us to
better understand and predict how such
disruptions impact Network performance
better respond to traffic incidents and
design more robust Road Networks
[Music]